thequiltshow.com 2015-09-14

# Privacy Notice

[](https://thequiltshow.com/privacy-notice#)  1

TheQuiltShow.com and its subsidiary companies respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted a corporate wide Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information you provide online.

We take our privacy policy seriously and you can expect to be notified of:

  * What personal information may be collected and by what means
  * Whether information is collected from children aged 12 and under
  * Who, if anyone, is collecting your personal information
  * How this information may be used, including, who - if anyone - it might be shared with
  * The consequences - if any - resulting from your refusal to provide personal information
  * How you can access and, if necessary, change the personal information a company maintains
  * How a company ensures data security, quality, and integrity
  * Where and how to ask questions or file complaints

ARJJ Inc. also adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles that were established by the U.S. Department of Commerce in consultation with the European Commission to comply with the European Commission's Directive on Data Protection that went into effect in October, 1998.

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our privacy statement or policies, please contact the Privacy Policy Administrator by writing to: TQS Privacy Policy Administrator, ARJJ Inc. Inc., P.O. Box 418, La Veta, CO 81055

**This privacy policy applies to the TheQuiltShow.com owned and operated by ARJJ Inc.**  
In addition, ARJJ Inc. may from time to time add new sites. Please note that this policy applies only to current or future sites maintained by ARJJ Inc. or its subsidiaries. This Privacy Policy does not apply to web sites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by ARJJ Inc. online, not offline.

**Third Party Sites**  
If you click on a link to a third party site, including our sponsor's, advertiser's or member's websites, you leave the ARJJ Inc. site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as ARJJ Inc.. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to an ARJJ Inc. site, you should consult that site's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

**What is personal information and when does TheQuiltshow collect it?**  
Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. ARJJ Inc. collects personal information from our online visitors during (1) the member registration, (2) contests (registration or claiming a prize), 3) warranty registration and/or during customer support or technical service requests, (4) marketing surveys and email campaigns, (5) when you order products or subscriptions from us online, (6) when you request services from third party service providers on our site, or (7) through the use of our online services.

Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, mobile number, home address, birth date and credit card information. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as gender, zip code, information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, media, Internet IP address and connection, information about online activity such as chat, message board postings and additional member profiles such as quilt information, shop information, and professional teacher's information. We may combine demographic information with personal information. In the event of contests, prize winners may also be required to provide Social Security or Social Identification Number for tax purposes.

Members must provide truthful account information in order to obtain access to most of the features on our site. Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent that is reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

**The Quilt Show's Online Store**  
Visitors purchasing goods and services through our online store may need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to name, mailing address(es), phone number and e-mail address.

**Online Chat Rooms and Profiles**  
You may choose to disclose information about yourself in our online chatrooms or when creating user "profiles" on our sites. Information that you disclose in chat rooms or in "profile" information is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in either place. Please see our Terms of Service on this point and for other guidelines about posting content on our web sites.

**A Special Note About Children**  
ARJJ Inc. encourages parents to spend time online with their children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers, without permission, when using the Internet. We recognize a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from young children. Therefore, children age 12 or younger are not permitted to become a member of The Quilt Show without written permission or other verifiable consent from a parent or guardian. A Consent Form is available upon request. This consent form must be completed, signed by a parent or legal guardian, and sent to ARJJ Inc., P.O. Box 418, La Veta, CO 81055. Once we validate this form, the appropriate permission form will be made available and instructions for registering will be provided. This form must be signed by the child's parent or guardian and returned to ARJJ Inc. by fax or mail to the Privacy Policy Administrator.

Once we have obtained parental consent and a child is registered, we are prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity - like contests - on the child's disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity.

If for any reason you are concerned that your child's personally identifiable information maintained by ARJJ Inc. is not correct or complete, should you wish to have your child's personal information deleted from our records, or if you want ARJJ Inc. to discontinue further collection or use of your child's personal information, please contact your Privacy Policy Administrator who will be happy to review, update or remove your child's information as appropriate.

**What about cookies and other technologies?**  
We use cookies and other technologies to passively collect demographic information, personalize your experience on our site and monitor advertisements and other activities. Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer to track movements within web sites. Certain of our sites use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. Also, we use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and for other purposes. We also use "cookies" or other methods to monitor website usage. We collect information on members activity within our site and which ads or links are clicked. We may link cookie information to personal information.

Some ads on our site may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads may be collected by our ad companies. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However some areas of our sites will not function properly if you do so.

Other technologies used include clear GIFs and IP address logging. Clear GIFs (a.k.a. web bugs, beacons or tags) are small graphic images placed on a web page, web-based document, or in an e-mail message. Clear GIFs are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (only 1-by-1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the web page, document or e-mail message. We do not use clear GIFs to collect personal information about you. However, we may use clear GIFs capture statistical usage information for our web pages, features or other elements on a web page. We may correlate this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on our web pages.

The Quilt Show also maintains log files which contain Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. In general, we only use log files to monitor traffic on our Web sites, to report aggregate information to our advertisers and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of user abuse of our websites, however, we may block certain IP addresses or console IDs provided by our licensed hardware manufacturers. IP addresses and console IDs may be linked to personal information.

**What happens to the information provided?**  
ARJJ Inc. does not disclose any personal information about children under 18 years of age who have registered on any of our websites to third parties, regardless of parental consent, or share or disclose personal information other than as set forth in this policy, provided however, that in the event of a merger, acquisition, or the unlikely event of bankruptcy, management of ARJJ Inc.' customer information may be transferred to its successor or assign.

The personal information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features and enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; and contests and events of interest. From time to time, we are approached by companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. In this event and at our discretion, The Quilt Show may send an email notice about the product or service, but it will not provide to the third-party your personal information.

We may use survey information in marketing surveys to select and direct advertising that is more likely to be of interest to a particular member. This information may be transmitted to an ad server owned by the advertising company to match members with ads that they are more likely to be interested in. However, we do not disclose any member's personal information to our advertisers without the member's consent. Participation in member surveys is entirely optional. We may share aggregate consumer data (which does not contain personal information) with the advertising companies.

From time to time, ARJJ Inc. may employ third-party contractors to collect personal information on our behalf, or to provide email delivery, product or promotional fulfillment, or other services on our sites. When requesting these services, you may be asked to supply your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address. When our third-party contractors collect and/or have access to the personal information you provide when requesting such services from ARJJ Inc., ARJJ Inc. requires that they adhere to our stated privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of personal information they collect or have access to in the course of their engagement by ARJJ Inc..

Finally, we may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can consistently improve our sites to better meet our visitors' needs. To enforce legal rights and the law, or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary to address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights, property, operations, users or others who may be harmed or may suffer loss or damage, we may also disclose personal information to law enforcement, or the appropriate civil authorities.

**Where is the information held?**  
ARJJ Inc. is a global organization but our database resides on our servers and backup servers the United States. Your personal information may be transferred to, used, processed or held by ARJJ Inc. in the United States and in other countries, including countries both in and outside the European Union, and used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

**Opt-out Provision**  
When we first collect information about you, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personal information shared with parties outside of ARJJ Inc. or its subsidiaries (except to the extent required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority). The Quilt Show newsletter is provided as part of your membership. You will not be able to opt out of newsletter receipt. If you do not wish to read it, you may delete it when it arrives, but the subscription will continue until membership is expires or is cancelled.

**Safeguarding Your Personal Information**  
We will only collect and use personal information in accordance with this privacy policy to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, accuracy and privacy of the information you have provided. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom we transfer any personal information will provide sufficient protection of that information.

**Review, Correction of Your Information and Requesting Removal from Mailing Lists and Deactivating Your Account**  
If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by ARJJ Inc. is not correct, or should you wish to have your account(s) deactivated please email the Privacy Policy Administrator. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our websites.

By using this site, you signify your assent to the ARJJ Inc. Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, you will not be able to register for membership thus preventing you from using any of the services provided on this site. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our web site to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our privacy policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Also, if there is a substantive change in the way that we use your personal information, we will notify you via e-mail of the relevant changes. If you choose to opt-out of our changed practice, our e-mail will contain instructions on how to opt-out. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Online Privacy Policy.
